Desmond Hill lives near Ashley Park .
B-Person I-Person O O B-Location I-Location O

I was skiing on Desmond Hill last winter when I met Ashley Park .
O O O O B-Location I-Location O O O O O B-Person I-Person O

Prime Minister Desmond Hill visited the victims of the flood at Ashley Park .
O O B-Person I-Person O O O O O O B-Location I-Location

Prime Minister Ashley Hill visited the victims of the flood at Desmond Park .
O O B-Person I-Person O O O O O O B-Location I-Location

Ashley Park is my hero .
B-Person I-Person O O O O

Desmond Park was the MVP of the year .
B-Person I-Person O O O O O O

People crowded at Desmond Park to see the show .
O O O B-Location I-Location O O O O O

Ashley Hill is my hero .
B-Person I-Person O O O O

Ashley Hill lives near Desmond Park .
B-Person I-Person O O B-Location I-Location O

I was skiing on Ashley Hill last year when I met Desmond Park .
O O O O B-Location I-Location O O O O O B-Person I-Person O

I got off the train at Desmond Park .
O O O O O O B-Location I-Location O

Desmond Hill got off the train at Ashley Park .
B-Person I-Person O O O O O B-Location I-Location O

Ashley Hill got off the train at Desmond Park .
B-Person I-Person O O O O O B-Location I-Location O

People crowded at Ashley Park to see the show .
O O O B-Location I-Location O O O O O

The commute from Ashley Park is terrible .
O O O B-Location I-Location O O O

The commute from Desmond Park is terrible .
O O O B-Location I-Location O O O

I voted for Desmond Hill .
O O O B-Person I-Person O

I voted for Ashley Hill .
O O O B-Person I-Person O

I voted at Ashley Park .
O O O B-Location I-Location O

I voted at Desmond Park .
O O O B-Location I-Location O

My sister lives in Ashley Park .
O O O O B-Location I-Location O

My sister is Ashley Hill .
O O O O B-Person I-Person O

My brother lives in Desmond Park .
O O O O B-Location I-Location O

My brother is Desmond Hill .
O O O O B-Person I-Person O
